<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WirelessMapper</string>
    <string name="edit_message">Enter a message</string>
    <string name="button_send">Send</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_name">[unnamed]</string>
    <string name="wifi_byte_to_ssid_pref_key">com.wiprof.wirelessprofiler.wifi_byte_to_ssid</string>
    <string name="wifi_ssid_to_index_pref_key">com.wiprof.wirelessprofiler.wifi_ssid_to_index</string>
    <string name="cellular_id_to_name_pref_key">com.wiprof.wirelessprofiler.cellular_id_to_name</string>
    <string name="cellular_type_to_index_pref_key">com.wiprof.wirelessprofiler.cellular_type_to_name</string>
    <string name="map_marker_pref_key">com.wiprof.wirelessprofiler.map_marker_pref_key</string>
    <string name="wifi_info_activity_title">WiFi Info</string>
    <string name="wifi_info_box_default_text">Tap on anything above to learn more.</string>
    <string name="wifi_ssid_attribute_info">
        &lt;b&gt;SSID&lt;/b&gt; stands for &lt;b&gt;S&lt;/b&gt;ervice &lt;b&gt;S&lt;/b&gt;et
        &lt;b&gt;ID&lt;/b&gt;entifier. It is the name of the WiFi network visible to the phone. &lt;br&gt;Different
        access points can have the same &lt;b&gt;SSID&lt;/b&gt; - they are not necessarily unique.
        Multiple access points with the same &lt;b&gt;SSID&lt;/b&gt; are often seen around large
        campuses, where an organization like a school or business might use several access points to
        extend a single WiFi network over a large area.
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_bssid_attribute_info">
        &lt;b&gt;BSSID&lt;/b&gt; stands for &lt;b&gt;B&lt;/b&gt;asic &lt;b&gt;S&lt;/b&gt;ervice &lt;b&gt;S&lt;/b&gt;et
        &lt;b&gt;ID&lt;/b&gt;entifier. It is a number which is unique to a specific access point. The access point
        uses it to identify itself to the phone and other computers over the internet. It is equivalent
        to the access point's MAC address.
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_capabilities_attribute_info">
        The &lt;b&gt;capabilities&lt;/b&gt; string gives certain technical information about
        the network. Here is a summary of some of the more common acronyms: &lt;/br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;WEP&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;WPA&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;WPA2&lt;/b&gt;: Signifies the method the network uses to encrypt
        your data. &lt;b&gt;WEP&lt;/b&gt; is the oldest and least secure method, while WPA2 is the newest and most secure.
        Any letters immediately following one of these separated by hyphens indicate more specific information
        about the access point\'s encryption and data transfer protocols.&lt;/br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;ESS&lt;/b&gt; stands for Extended Service Set, meaning that this access point is one of multiple
        that all share the same network.
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_frequency_attribute_info">
        The &lt;b&gt;frequency&lt;/b&gt; a WiFi access point can determine its range and speed. Higher frequencies
        (in the 5000 Mhz range) will allow data transfer but can only operate over a relatively small area.
        Lower frequencies (in the 2400 Mhz range) serve a wider range at the cost of slower service speed.
        Access points with frequencies too close together (within 10 Mhz) can interfere and cause data
        loss and therefore slower speeds.
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_channel_attribute_info">
        The &lt;b&gt;channel&lt;/b&gt; is a number assigned to a specific frequency. To avoid interfering
        with other types of wireless signals like BlueTooth or cellular signals, only certain frequencies
        can be used for WiFi, and each of these is given a channel number by convention.
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_access_point_attribute_info">
        This box shows basic information about a WiFi wireless &lt;b&gt;access point&lt;/b&gt;. "Access point" here
        signifies the physical router that is transmitting the WiFi signal. A WiFi network is composed
        of one or more access points.&lt;/br&gt;
        The icon to the left of the box indicates the strength of the signal received by your phone
        from this access point.&lt;/br&gt;
        To the right of the icon is the name of the access point, consisting of
        the name (SSID) of the WiFi network and, optionally, a number to differentiate access points
        with the same SSID. Note that this number is not actually determined by anything about the
        access point itself, but is assigned by this app to the access points in the order they are
        first seen, and so may differ from phone to phone.&lt;/br&gt;
        On the right side of the box is the numerical value of the power (strength) of the WiFi signal, given
        in two different units. Dbm (decibel-milliwatts) is a logarithmic unit, so that increasing
        the number by ten actually indicates an increase of ten &lt;i&gt;times&lt;/i&gt; the power.
        Pw (picowatts) is a normal linear unit, so doubling the number indicates a doubling of power.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_pin_map">Pin Map</string>
    <string name="no_signal_message">no signal</string>
    <string name="wifi_strength_dbm_format">%d Dbm</string>
    <string name="wifi_strength_label_text">Strength</string>
    <string name="pin_timestamp_label_text">Creation Time</string>
</resources>
